The morning chimes have sounded, and it's us, the Shoe Evisuers!
The Bad Faces Ebisu Qualifying Tournament!
You've heard of "bad face," right?
It's something, you know, in our hometown.
Preliminary round? Qualifying?
Yes, sir! Well, you all know this one.
This is a parody of a well-known YouTube project.
It is important to hold a qualifying competition first, with the intention of going out for real someday.
It's important.
It's important. So, you see, we already have a lot of bad faces here,
Then, we don't know each other, right?
You don't know each other, do you? What don't we know?
Let's look at them one by one.
Here is the first one.
Oh! Me!
Oh! I knew it!
It looks amazing from the start.
Wow.
Wow. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's white... like this, I guess.
It's what you're wearing.
You're not trying to hide, are you?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry to all of you.
I feel really bad.
It's really bad.
He's got a really bad look in his eyes.
This is so bad.
What did you really do?
I stole some yakisoba bread from a bakery.
That's bad.
Bad, bad, bad.
That's so bad.
You should pay for that.
That's so bad!
That's what you're paying for.
I could have bought melon bread.
I couldn't get the yakisoba bread.
I couldn't buy it.
We're running out of time.
Patience.
Oh! Oh!
It looks like there's a picture of Maima's outfit.
I coordinated it to match the day.
And then there was the radio show.
Oh, no.
Oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wow, it's so colorful in there.
It really stands out, like I'm about to steal it.
Oh, yeah.
These pants.
Are these pants bad?
You know, I took them down for the occasion.
That's right.
You're really into this.
I'm really into it.
You're really into it.
I see.
But you look really bad.
You look bad.
You look really bad.
No, that's good. I'm going to go alone.
Shall we continue?
Let's continue.
I don't know who that is.
Oh! Emma!
Emma.
You look bad.
I can't even imagine.
Oh, my God, it's so bad.
It's in the wrong place.
I'm getting something.
What?
It's bad for the guy who's getting it.
What are you getting?
It's bad.
I hid something.
Oh, shit! Bad!
My bad!
Oh, shit! This is a little...
Are you okay? I'm not supposed to show you this, am I?
What are you doing? Are you serious?
What is this? Maybe it's the guy who's supposed to give it to her.
The receiver? Some kind of expo crackdown.
This isn't good, is it?
That's high.
What are you getting? This.
I wonder what it is.
It's... it's medicine, but it's Biofermin!
Your tummy hurts, doesn't it?
I know, right? That's comforting.
I liked the Biofermin.
Good!
That's great! They got it.
You shouldn't have done this when you were 15.
I shouldn't have done that.
Next is Cocona Sakuragi.Then Cocona Sakuragi.
What a... handful.
It's over!
It's not over!
You tricked me, didn't you?
What's this?
Squidgy.
He never gets his hands dirty.
And the way he curls his hair... it's kind of intense.
Close, close, close.
You've got some serious eyes.
What was the crime?
What? Is that what this is?
Not to follow up on Emma from earlier, but...
Where do you deliver the drugs? Something like that.
Isn't that what he's going to do? This guy.
He's calling, isn't he?
Purposeful.
I see what you're getting at.
I found a date show.
Oh, my God.
You're trying to trick me, but...
But you're making sweet noises.
You're making a bad face.
I'm gonna get suckered in.
That's it!
Alirico!
Alirico.
What's he saying, but he looks kind of smart.
You seem to be in a hurry.
Aren't you tired? She's tired.
She seems tired.
That's for sure.
She is tired.
I'm Riko Nagayama when I'm tired.
I'm feeling a little impatient. I wonder what this is.
I sold some fake jewelry at a jewelry store.
I'm in a hurry to escape through the back door.
I'm getting caught.
You're in a hurry.
She's in a bit of a hurry.
I wonder what she's up to.
Selling just a body cream, claiming it's a slimming cream.
It's a scam.
If she looks like this, I'm sure I'll believe her.
It sure looks like a scam.
Scam face.
It's a scam.
I'm here with seven other people.
What's going on?
What's that?
You think I'm getting the hang of this? This.
What's that? The pills you just took.
Oh, I'm talking about this.
What is it?
I don't know.
Oh!
Pull it out.
This is good. This is good.
You know what I mean.
Because I just got the pills out.
Pills.
You know what?
You got them.
We traded it for more.
You mean the Japanese word "pos"?
"Pos" is not "pos".
That's not good.
Isn't it?
No, it's a person's name.
Resale of tickets at a high price.
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
We'll tell you.
No! Absolutely.
You can't resell it.
No, but that's a resale face, that's for sure.
Pull it.
I got it! I got the money! It's like...
I sold it for a little bit more.
Please go through the proper channels.
That's right.
We'll go through the regular channels.
Representing the voice of the artist.
Absolutely not.
I see.
Oh, you mean with Mr. God help us.
God help me.
I'm electronic these days, so I didn't know what it was.
That's why we're electronic.
That's for sure.
Oh, don't say that.
I don't have an image of you, do I?
Yuna.
Yuna.Yuuna.
Such a young girl.
What is it? There's something here.
The pickup's bad.
I looked this way.
It's not that one.
It's from the candy shop.
It's Manjikabe!
He said, "It's Manabe.
I'm Manabe Nanaya.
Like elementary school kids.
I see.
I think it's simply violence.
Simple violence.
After you do it.
Yes, after you do it.
After you hit him.
I hit him.
I wonder what it is.
Maybe it's the story behind the sketch.
I knew it!
Fear.
I'm right.
This...
This walk is fear.
Fear.
I think I'm going to get a good look at this.
Crew video
Oh, here we go
Let's take a look.
I don't know what to say.
The low angle.
I know.
It's... it's...
It's...
Something's different.
Hey!
Oh, no!
He's so cute!
Awkward! Awkward!
I wanna see it again! I wanna see it again!
Hey!
I just want it to look good!
Maybe I'm getting used to it!
I'm not used to it!
Next, Iro?
Let's go, Iro-san!
Thank you for watching.
Change?
He wants his change.
You want change?
Who wants change?
You seem like a low man.
He seemed like the lowest man on the block.
Like, go check it out.
I think that's it.
Yuna under duress.
Under duress.
Go check the change.
Go give it to her.
Go make a decision on the change.
What's this?
Baba the cat.
Neko Baba.
You've got the guts to do something big.
You two.
You two are elementary school students.
It fits the character.
Yes, they do.
Next, Mr. Kawao.
Here we go.
Please.
Atypical.
That's not good.
Eh?
A little bad.
ay.
Yes, sir.
It's a container car.
I don't know...
Ah!
Ebi chun ebi chun
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Ebichung Ebichung
Ebichung artist
Not Ebichung
Yes, um...
Not the scandal one.
No, no, no...
The stalker.
Yes, the stalker.
Oh.
I'm the stalker.called
uh...
I mean...
You're stalking me.
Doubtful.
I doubt it.
Because Rico...
He doesn't seem that scared.
I don't know...
I'm like... "Why don't you notice how weird this is?
I mean...
From that distance...
I saw it 10 times.
I've already recorded it.
What?
That's the distance.
Oh, my God.
You look happy.
Val is here.
You're being stalked.
We need to get out of here faster.
They've already got him.
This is a bit of a problem for Mr. Nakayama.
I do have a problem.
My comment was perfect.
Did you do it?
I didn't.
Actually, it doesn't sound familiar.
Did you?
That's bad.
That's the worst you've ever done.
I'm coming in hard.
If he says he's coming, he's coming hard.
I'm coming, I'm risking it.
I'm coming, I'm coming hard.
I can see it.
I'm going to do it.
Fingers?
Who are you?
του 작
What?
Are you tired?
I'm tired of this.
Tired?
What do you mean, "change rings"?
Changing rings?
It looked like a café.
It looked like a café that I've seen before.
We went to a place called Shrimp Tube Cafe.
That's where it was held.
I don't know.
A ring change.
It's pretty obvious.
Do you have this?
Multi.
Multi rings
If you buy this, you will be happy, right?
Ring scheme?
Ring sales
Look at this... and I'll make you happy.
You use it to negotiate.
Negotiations break down.
I'm anticipating something with the other guy.
What the hell is this?
What's this?
Marriage sign.
I owe Yoon-ho so much for this.
Is that a member's ring?
I borrowed the members' rings.
I was wondering which one I should get.
"Which one do I give my favorite ring to?
It's so funny how he gave out the rings.
What to give out...
Closely worn.
The kind you get as a novelty or something.
Closely-worn clothes
This is also Helfon Juno's personal belongings.
Marriage Sign
perfect fit
It fits perfectly.
I'm sorry.
Did you know?
Just between you and me.
I told you to keep your mouth shut.
I wouldn't go that far.
That's what you said in the first place.
I'm just saying...
So, we're the winners, right?
We're still down to our last man.
It could be a hell of a lot worse.
The last one.
That's a pretty high bar.
Who's the last one?
Yasumoto's not answering.
Someone's here.
He's here.
I wonder...
Everyone is laughing
Seikin REACTSeikin REACT
Let's do it again.
Let's do it one more time.
I think I understand something about this.
Haha this I bought.
That's what it is, eating and running away, isn't it?
Yahaha, behind you, don't know if you're good or not, don't know if you're good or not, don't know if you're good or not, don't know if you're good or not, give me good stuff.
I wonder if he's got a hold of me... I wonder if he's got a hold of me... I wonder if he's got a hold of me...
You're so cool!
You're trying to be cool. You're trying to be cool.
You're trying to be cool, you're trying to be cool.
I wonder which one is everyone's favorite.
I'm trying to be cool, but it's a bad look, so I'm trying to be cool.
But if it's bad, it's bad... I wonder if I could have gotten away with it...
I could feel the drama in the air.
The winner of the Bad Faces Ebisu Qualifying Contest is...
The winner of the Bad Face Ebisu Qualifying Contest is...
Aaaaaaah!
9th place, super-neat!
Buuuuut... I have a sudden sound announcement...
I'm so happy to announce that Erjun Cafe will be held in Sendai as well!
I'm not going to eat with my marriage partner!
The period is from June 1st to June 24th. Please visit us and don't miss out on the food!
I added 5 bouvernies to the menu.
I am PROFESSOR 7
i am PROFESSOR 7
I wonder if they are connected?
Yes, they are.
Like the opening.
I guess so.
I don't like it. People think it would be nice if that ace was connected to this ace.
There are a lot of them.
It's embarrassing.
Well then, everyone, please come and visit us as EbiChu Cafe for our spring tour.
Well, that was us, Chusen Stuark.
Bye bye.
Please give us a like or a good button.
See you soon.
Bye bye.